Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, circa 1985-2005; Accession ARCH-2010-106
  - Americas y Latinas (Journal of Women and Gender), 1992-1998; Subseries 2
    - Americas and Latinas Documents (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Krause Videos (Clasa Media Task Force) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Publication – Enlace 1990s, Subseries 3
    - Musicians brought to Stanford -- 90s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Musician Juan Sanchez 1998 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Flor de Caña In concert 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Club (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Online Publicity / Distribution lists (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Latin American Studies Association Member Directory (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Mail Services (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Email Distribution Lists (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Mailing List Request forms (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Center’s Mailing List, Planning and Input (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Chile Mailing Lists (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Films about Latin America (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Events and Services Info (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - On Campus Rental Facilities (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Off campus Rental Facilities (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Printers/Copy Services (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Party/Rental Information (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Photographers Information (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Translation and Interpretation Services (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Enlace 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Enlace Style Sheet (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Enlace Publication – Spring 1998 – Copy 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Enlace Publication – Spring 1998 – Copy 2 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Enlace in Progress – Bid Estimates (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Design – Printing – Enlace 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - 97/98 Enlace Mailing (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Draft Articles - Enlace 1997 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Alumni News for 1997 Enlace (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Articles, Ideas for Enlace 97 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - New Articles for BIRD (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Enlace Publication - Fall 1995 - Copy 1,2 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Enlace 1996 - Photos Info (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 1996 Faculty Research Request (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - 1996 Enlace Mailing (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Enlace ideas, suggestions 1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Enlace Publication - Fall 1996 - Copy 1 (Box 8, Folder 3637)
    - Enlace 1996 General Info, Outline (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Enlace 1996 Draft Articles (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Enlace 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Enlace 95 Mailing (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Enlace 95 – 149 Off campus receivers of the publication (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Enlace 1995 – 122 On Campus addresses to receive the publication (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Alumni Fundraising appeal (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Enlace 1995 Fundraising Appeal around 360 Alumni (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Enlace Fall 1995 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Draft Articles 1995 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Documents for Enlace 1995 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Documents for Enlace 1994 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Enlace Publication - Summer 1992 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Enlace Publication - Summer 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5152)
    - Documents for Enlace 1993 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Newsletter Mailing 1993 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - LAS Newsletters 1984-89 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Old Enlaces (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - CLAS Publications – General Info (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1994– Copy 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Newsletters – Other Depts., Programs (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sample Newsletters - Other Programs (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Interactions IIS Fall 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Interactions IIS Spring 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Latin American Studies Student Handbook 97-98 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Aid, Subseries 4
    - Budget – Grad Aid Formulas (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Airport Transportation Information (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Grad Aid 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Grad Aid 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - LAS Graduate Aid 01-02 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Global Exchange Info (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Pan American Society (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Global Exchange / Brazilian Women Project (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Inter-American Development Bank (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - La Pena - Berkeley (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - RYSE / Caius Brandao (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - World Forum Information (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - World Affairs Council, Commonwealth Club, etc. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - United Nations Association Info (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Intel / Tech Contacts (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - LCT Language Programs - US (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - UCB / Stanford Colloquium Spring 1995 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Fall Faculty Colloquium Stanford 11/94 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - UCB Core Faculty (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Health & Safety - OSHA (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Facilities – Fire & Safety (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Facilities Costs (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Facilities Activity 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Latin American Consulates in San Francisco (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence - Consulates (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Back up Information for Community Service Database (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Outreach Ideas (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Visitors, Requests for Collaboration (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - K-12 / Community College Outreach (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Arts Cooperative – Chiapas Mexico (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - School Programs / Curriculum (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Andean Working Group (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - LAS Programs at other Universities (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Other LAS Centers/ newsletters (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Tinker Cost Share (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Tinker Visiting Professors (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Scholarship / Fellowship Students (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Summer Field Research Grant (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - 2001 Honors College (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Working Groups - General (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Working Group Info / Correspondence 1999/2000 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Working Group Lists (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Latin American Studies Association Member Directory 1996 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Latin American Studies Association Member Directory 1995-96 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - LASA Info (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence with IIS (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - GSB Brazil Study Trip 12/1999 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Stanford Language Center (Brochures) (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Overseas Studies (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - SPICE Stanford Program on International and Cross-Cultural Education 1999 Catalog (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - SPICE, STEP (Stanford Teaching Education Program) BAGEP (Bay Area Global Education Program) Info (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - UNAM / Stanford Teacher Workshop 5/13/95 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - School of Education Information Bulletin 94-95 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Sample Posters/ Brochures for Events (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Salary Setting 01-02 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - Salary Setting 02-03 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Events Outreach, 1993-1997; Subseries 5
    - Modern Language Association of America (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Galleries, Cultural Centers, etc. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Museum/ Art Outreach Ideas (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Central America Website / Incorpore (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Speaker Info: Ruth Cardoso (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Campus Maps (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Parking Information (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Mexican Studies Working Group (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Working Group on Women and Gender (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Student Theses / Paper/ Internships and Advisors 98-01 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - SPILS (Stanford Program in Legal Studies) Info (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Student Group Contacts (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Central America Working Group (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Community Health Working Group (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Democratization Seminar (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Bolivar House Logo (originals) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Invitations for Events (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - General Info on Publicity (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Flyers – Spring 2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Flyer / Calendar Letterhead (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Asians in Latin America Working Groups (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Brazil Working Group (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Media Contacts / Requests for info (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Media Resources (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Daily Advertising (LAS Ads) (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Stanford Daily: Contracts and Rates (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Stanford Network / Channel 51 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Stanford Daily / Other Publicity (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Old Title VI, Sample Title VI, Proposals – Other Centers, Subseries 6
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Title VI 94-95 JUTTA (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Title VI 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Question on IEUZ404 _ 97-98 Title VI (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Title VI UC Berkeley IEUZ407 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Title VI UC Berkeley 1995-96 1EUZ407 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Title VI UC Berkeley 1EUZ449 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Title VI Subcontract – UC Berkeley PR 8800 & Amendments (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Title VI commencing August 15, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Title VI Proposal 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Degree/ Career Reports 90-91, 91-92, 92-93 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Title VI 89-90 Report (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Grant Proposals 1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Title VI Proposal 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Title VI Proposals - Past (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Title VI – Performance Report 91-92 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Title VI – 1990 – 1991 Perform Report (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Title VI Performance Reports - Past (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Berkeley – Stanford Title VI Mtgs (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Federal Lobbying Effort 1995 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Title VI Lobbying Effort – 1995/1996 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Application for Continuation of Title VI 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Title VI 1992-1993 Proposal (Continuation) (Box 10, Folder 4.819921993E9)
    - Sponsored Project Proposal P015A10006 (Box 10, Folder 4950)
    - 1995-96 Performance Report (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 1993-94 Program Report (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Title VI Performance Report 94-95 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Title VI 1992-1993 Performance Report (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Title VI 1994-97 Cycle Results (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - State of the World Forum 1998 Invitation (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - A Collaborative Research Venture (Stanford, UPenn, U of Michigan) (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Autoridad de la Region Interoceanica Info Folder 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Autoridad de la Region Interoceanica Info Folder 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - City of Knowledge Attendee Information (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - City of Knowledge Logistics (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - City of Knowledge – Correspondence (KM and R. Paredes) (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - SPICE General Info (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - UN 50 SPICE Unit (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - National Foreign Language Week Unit (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - SPICE Migration Longview Proposal (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Outreach Conference AEGIS/SPICE/NRC’s 11/92 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - CFLISP/ CISP / BAGEP (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - SPICE-ADMIN / Personnel (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - SPICE – Irvine Grant (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - SPICE – Materials in Development (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Lucia Nuñez – SPICE (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Tinker Scholars, Subseries 7
    - Fernando Birri (Tinker) Fall/Winter/Spring 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Fernando Birri – Tinker 01-02 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Fernando Birri (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Juan Gasto Visiting Scholar Environmental Policy 2002 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Roger Bartra Winter 01-02 Tinker (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Roger Bartra 01-02 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Rosanna Reguillo Fall/ Win 01-02 Tinker (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Rosanna Reguillo Continued (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Luis Lumbreras Winter 00-01 Tinker (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Luis Lumbreras Continued (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Alejandro Mohar Tinker Chair 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Di Tella, Torcuato Tinker 1999-00 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Di Tella, Torcuato Tinker 1999-00 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Kuntz-Ficker, Sandra Tinker W-S 1998-99 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Kuntz-Ficker, Sandra Tinker W-S 1998-99 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Kuntz-Ficker, Sandra Tinker W-S 1998-99 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Lorenzo Meyer Tinker 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Lorenzo Meyer Tinker 98-99 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Carlos Marichal Tinker 1998-99 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Carlos Marichal Tinker 1998-99 Continued (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Falcon, Romana Tinker 1996-97 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Falcon, Romana Tinker 1996-97 continued (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Sarukhan, Jose Tinker 97-98 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Sarukhan, Jose Tinker 97-98 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Gilly, Adolfo Tinker 96-97 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Gilly, Adolfo Tinker 96-97 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Gonzalez Stephan, Beatriz Tinker (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Maria Herminia Tavares de Almeida (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Ruben Zamora Tinker 95-96 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Rafael Zamarrina Tinker 96-97 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Eduardo Lizano Tinker 94-95 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Eduardo Lizano Tinker 94-95 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Eduardo Viola Tinker 93-94 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Augusto Monteroso Tinker 92-93 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Eduardo Galeano 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Eduardo Galeano 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Monica Hirst (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Rodolfo Stavenhagen Tinker 91-92 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Monica Hirst Tinker 91-92 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Rodolfo Stavenhagen Tinker 91-92 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Rosalbra Campra Tinker 1989-90 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Juan Martinez Tinker 1988-89 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Stefano Varese, Tinker 1986-87 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Perdomo, Rogelio Tinker 1982-83 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Tinker/Nabuco Visiting Scholars 1998 to date (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Visiting Professors Handbook 01-02 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - 1999-00, 2001-02 Knight Fellows (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Former Tinker / Nabuco Scholars, 1996-2006; Subseries 8
    - Buscaglia Tinker 05-06 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Cueto Tinker 05-06 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Glantz Tinker 05-06 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Queiroz (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Fernando Birri Spring 03 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Alberto Ruy Sanchez Spring 03 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Luiz M. Ocampo Winter 01-02 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Isidoro Cheresky 02-03 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Eliseo Subiela 02-03 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Isidoro Cheresky 02-03 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Alfredo Molano 02-03 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Constanza Ocampo Lecturer Latinam 165C Spring ‘04 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Marcello Buchelli, Lecturer Fall 03-04 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Clara Nicholls, Lecturer Fall 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Eligio Fernandez Lecturer/artist Spring 03 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Constanza Ocampo 02-03Pre-field Research Seminar (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Renato Ortiz (Nabuco) Winter 02-03 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Alba Zaluar (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Simon Schwartzman Nabuco Chair 00 Winter 00-01 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Simon Schwartzman Nabuco (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Jose Murillo Nabuco Chair Win-Spr 98-99 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Milton Santos Nabuco Chair W98 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Milton Santos (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Milton Santos Nabuco Chair Winter 98 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Jose Goldemberg Nabuco Chair 96-97 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Jose Goldemberg (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Visiting Scholars, Subseries 9
    - Visiting scholar cards (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - How to request a J1 Visa online (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Exit form for Departing Visiting scholars (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Dinner in Honor of Visiting Faculty 2001 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Business Cards order form for Visiting scholars (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Chris Duffield Visiting Scholar 02-03 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Maria Guerra Visiting scholar 02-03 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Joan Kruckewitt Summer, fall, winter 02-03 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Katia Aida Silva Visiting 03 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Gregory Scott 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Emily Yates-Doerr (Visiting Scholar 02-03) (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - David Gamache Hutchinson 01-02 Fulbright Scholar (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Poemysl Macha 2001-02 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Visiting Scholars from Comparative Literature – Betania Mariani/Jose L. Jobin (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Roshni Rustomji-Kerns 2001-02 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Josefina Alcazar 1/1/02 – 3/30/02 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Joao Almino (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Maria Fernanda Arias (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Sergio de Azevedo (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Mauro Barbosa Almeida Jan-June 2002 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Marcelo Bernardo Barrios (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Oscar Arturo Benavides Gonzalez 1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Arturo Arias (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Oscar Benavides G. Visiting Scholar 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Charles J Beirne, S.J. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Willi Bolle 7/1/99 – 2/29/00 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Renato Boschi 1990 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Bouchra Bounoua 00-01 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Helena Bousquet Bomeny (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Roberto Bouzas (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Gordon Brotherson (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Alison Brysk 1/96 – 7/96 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Tony + Cecilia Burciaga (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Desiree Elizondo Cabrera (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Chuck Call (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Daniel Caceres 02-03 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Leon Campbell (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Gabriela Cano Sept 01- June 02 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Cesar Cansino Visiting Scholar 1989-90 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Ana Sofia Cardenal (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Jean Casimir Visiting Prof. 1998-1999 fall quarter (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Carlos Fernando Chamorro (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Graciela Chichilnisky (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Tom Cohen (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - David Collier (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Tarcisio Costa (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Prof. Ann Craig (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Jose Cuellar (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Benedita Da Silva (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Mauricio Davila-Sanchez (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Juan Manuel Delgado M. Visiting Scholar 1998-99 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Ponciano Del Pino Dec. 99 – June 30 2000 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Steve Diamond (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Carolina Diaz-Walls (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Kathleen Dill March 27-Aug. 31 2001 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Graciela Ducatenzeiler 1995-96 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Chris Duffield (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Durham, Kathleen Foote (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Javier Elguea Visiting Scholar 1989-90 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Mark Eisner (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Keith Ellis (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Antonio Eligio Fernandez (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Patricia Fernandez de Castro (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Carlos Figueroa Ibarra (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Rubem Fonseca (Box 14, Folder 67)
    - Clemente Forero June – Oct 99 (Box 14, Folder 68)
    - Marusa Freire July 01-02 (Box 14, Folder 69)
    - Julio Garcia Espinoza Dolores Calvino (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Juan Diego Garcia Prieto (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Juan Gasto Coderch – Environmental Fellow 01-02 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Veronique Gauthier 1995-96 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Barbara Geddes (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Silvia Gerschman de Leis (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Jorge Ramon Gonzalez Ponciano (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Ramon Gonzalez 90-91 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Soledad Gonzalez Montes Visiting Scholar 1998-99 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Elena Granell de Aldaz (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Greg Greenway (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Marcelo Gumucio 9/1/01 – 8/31/02 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Maria Angeles Guzman Summer 1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Jerry Haar Summer 1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Conference on Lat Ame Banking (Haber, Julie Anderson, Steinmueller) 1/93 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Reiner Enrique Hamel / Maria Teresa Sierra 9/1/93 – 8/14/94 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Manuel Hidalgo (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Nickie Irvine: Runa Resource Management Film Project Proposal (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Patrick Hunt (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Jane Jaquette Jan-June 2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - John Johnson (Emeritus) (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Bruce Johnston (Emeritus) (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Jorge Guillermo Jan 5th – April 7th 2002 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Weina Karlsson (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Miriam Kornblith 4/1/88 – 10/7/91 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Efrain Kristal (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Gino Lofredo 1994-95 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Luis Leal (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Victoria Lerner (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Doug Libby Jan. 94 – Jan 1995 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Jose Augusto Lindgren Alves (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Lipset, Seymour Martin (Sociology) (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Edgar de Magalhaes (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ernesto Medina (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Brian Meeks Summer 1999 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Lynn Meisch (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Ellen Messer (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Fabian Armando Michleangeli (Biological Sciences) 94-95 Ayacucho (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Claudio Millman 6/12/00 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Alejandro Mohar (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Jose Montalvo (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Roxana Morduchowicz (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Vania Moreira 9/15/99 – 8/15/00 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Luis Moreno Ocampo (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Richard Morse (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Douglas Murray (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Bernardo Navarrete 10/3/98-10/3/99 Visiting Scholar (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Maria Izabel Noll (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Rigoberto Ocampo Alcantar (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Andre Odenbreit Carvalho (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Jocelyn Olcott (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Marietta Ortega - Social and Cult. Anthropology CASA (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Arturo Pacheco (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Vera Paiva (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Charles Pearson (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Robert Stuart Pelton (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Enrique Penalos Visiting Scholar 1/12/01 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Heloisa Pontes 01-02 (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - David Post Sept. 99 – June 2000 (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Pilar Ramirez (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Pilar Ramirez Continuation (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - Maria Luisa Ramos Summer 1994 (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Anna Carolina Regner (Box 15, Folder 63)
    - Ademar Romeiro Fall 1994 (Box 15, Folder 64)
    - Hector Rueda de Leon (Box 15, Folder 65)
    - Jorge Rufinelli (Box 15, Folder 66)
    - Apen Ruiz (Box 15, Folder 67)
    - Jose Ruiz San Roman (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Roshni Rustomji-Kerns (Box 15, Folder 69)
    - Oswaldo Sala 93-94 (Box 15, Folder 70)
    - Eneas Salati (Box 15, Folder 71)
    - Brasilio Sallum Jr. (Box 15, Folder 72)
    - Judit Sandor Visiting Scholar 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 73)
    - Carlos Guilherme Santos Seroa da Mota (Box 15, Folder 74)
    - Carlos Guilherme Santos Seroa da Mota (Continued) (Box 15, Folder 75)
    - Alvaro Zerda Sarmiento 98-99 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Suzana Sawyer (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - T.M. Scruggs Summer 1999 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Maria Teresa Sierra (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Joel Simon Media Fellow Fall 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Robert Slenes 93-94 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Hazel Smith (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Luiz Soares (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Staven Hagen (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Stolcke – Martinez Alier (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Bill Summerhill Fall 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Maria Hermina Tavares de Almeida (Box 16, Folder 12)